<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DiorPay</string>
    <string name="asset1">Asset</string>
    <string name="trade1">Market</string>
    <string name="market1">News</string>
    <string name="mine1">Me</string>
    <string name="start_en">Never let down your trust.</string>
    <string name="start_zh">因为信任 绝不辜负</string>
    <string name="register">Sign up</string>
    <string name="num_pwd">Set up password</string>
    <string name="num_pwd1">Change password</string>
    <string name="pwd_sure">Confirm payment password</string>
    <string name="pwd_sure1">Payment password successfully changed!</string>
    <string name="gesture_pwd">Gesture password</string>
    <string name="old_gesture_pwd">Current gesture password</string>
    <string name="gesture_pwd_again">Re-verify</string>
    <string name="change_gesture_pwd">Change gesture password</string>
    <string name="toast_gesture_error">Wrong gesture password, you still have</string>
    <string name="toast_gesture_error1">changes!</string>
    <string name="toast_gesture_success">Gesture password successfully saved!</string>
    <string name="toast_gesture_error2">Five chances has been used up, please login again!</string>
    <string name="toast_gesture_diff">Different gesture password!</string>
    <string name="info_tip">We need to know more information for better wallet management.</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip">Please enter 6 digital numbers for payment password.</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip1a">Enter origin payment password</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip1">Please enter origin payment password!</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip2a">Enter new payment password</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip2">Please enter new payment password!</string>
    <string name="pwd_tip3">Please enter confirm payment password!</string>
    <string name="gesture_tip">Tip:gesture password needs at least 5 connected points!</string>
    <string name="hint_wallet_name">Set up wallet name</string>
    <string name="wallet_name">Wallet name</string>
    <string name="hint_mobile">Please enter your phone number</string>
    <string name="toast_mobile">Please enter correct phone number</string>
    <string name="mobile">Phone number</string>
    <string name="hint_code">Please enter verification code</string>
    <string name="code">Verification code</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="collect">Receive</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="sure">Confirm</string>
    <string name="login">Log in</string>
    <string name="create_wallet">Create wallet</string>
    <string name="read_agree">I have read and agreed</string>
    <string name="service_privacy"><u>Service and privacy protocol</u></string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright © 2018-2019 Diorpay</string>
    <string name="toast_pwd">Please enter 6 digital password!</string>
    <string name="toast_sure_pwd">Please make sure the password is the same twice!</string>
    <string name="jump">Skip</string>
    <string name="asset">Asset</string>
    <string name="trade">Market</string>
    <string name="market">News</string>
    <string name="mine">Me</string>
    <string name="pwd_img">Password image</string>
    <string name="collect_coin">Collect coin</string>
    <string name="send_coin">Send coin</string>
    <string name="address">Receiving address</string>
    <string name="address0">Address</string>
    <string name="count">Amount</string>
    <string name="group">Available: </string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="ps">Remarks</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="personal_asset">Personal Asset</string>
    <string name="no_data">No data</string>
    <string name="transaction_record">Transaction record</string>
    <string name="exchange">Market</string>
    <string name="currency">Coin</string>
    <string name="new_praise">Price</string>
    <string name="chg">Change</string>
    <string name="notice">Notice</string>
    <string name="hot">Hot</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="update">Edit</string>
    <string name="message">Messages</string>
    <string name="message_center">Message center</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="about">About us</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="select_language">Language</string>
    <string name="profile">\u3000\u3000As a safe and convenient digital asset management tool, DiorPay has the features of security prevention and control technology, instant transfer, etc., to provide you with real-time bitcoin market, Ethereum and other popular currency market trends, download DiorPay a wallet, you can manage more Currency. At the same time provide the latest market, real-time updates, help you invest and manage more peace of mind. </string>
    <string name="agreement">Use Agreement</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="version_log">Version log</string>
    <string name="check_new">Check for updates</string>
    <string name="help0">How to create a wallet?</string>
    <string name="help0_a">xxxxxxx</string>
    <string name="help1">How to back up the wallet/identity?</string>
    <string name="help1_a">In DiorPay, we introduced the concept of digital identity, for a digital identity, you can click here for a detailed explanation. So how do we back up the wallet/identity?\n1. Click on \"My\" -> and then click on the avatar button at the top to enter my identity interface.\n2. Click \"Backup Identity\" and enter the password when creating the identity.\n3. Start backing up the identity, please copy the mnemonic in order. For how to safely back up the mnemonic, you can click here for detailed explanation.\nPS: When you create a digital identity, the digital identity will correspond to a wallet address, the DOB\'s wallet address, and the identity you backed up, which is also the mnemonic for this address.</string>
    <string name="help2">What digital currencies does DiorPay support?</string>
    <string name="help2_a">DiorPay is a cross-chain wallet that currently supports SAS BZF DOB ETH BTC and other ERC20 compliant tokens\nIn addition, users can see for themselves whether the tokens they want to search meet the ERC20 standard:\n<a href="https://etherscan.io/tokens">https://etherscan.io/tokens</a></string>
    <string name="help3">Can the digital currency type displayed on the wallet homepage be modified?</string>
    <string name="help3_a">No</string>
    <string name="help4">How to transfer/receive?</string>
    <string name="help4_a">Go to the wallet asset interface and go to the wallet list page. Select the wallet you want to use. Take the DOB wallet as an example. Go to the Assets page and click on a token in the list to see its detailed page. At the bottom there are two buttons - collection and transfer.\nTip: Of course, you can also use the asset items that you want to transfer or collect money to quickly operate the collection and transfer operations.\nClick the payment button to enter the payment page. In this page, the top character is the address of the wallet, the middle is the QR code corresponding to the address, and the bottom is \"asset name\" and \"transfer amount\".\nFor the payment without the amount limit, you can copy the address string or QR code directly to the transfer party. This address string is different from the two-dimensional code and the private key or mnemonic. You can send it to others with confidence, without worrying about security issues.\nIf you encounter a payment that requires a specified amount. You can click the \"Specify Amount\" button in the lower right corner, enter the amount of the amount in the pop-up amount box, and click OK.\nClick the \"Transfer\" button in the lower right corner of the asset interface to enter the asset transfer interface. Here, take the DOB as an example, enter the amount to be transferred, and fill in the remarks if necessary. Enter the other party\'s wallet address in the payment address.</string>
    <string name="help5">Is DiorPay charged? What is the rate?</string>
    <string name="help5_a">xxxxxxx</string>
    <string name="help6">How to change the password? What if I forget my password?</string>
    <string name="help6_a">First, in the decentralized wallet, because all user authentication content, such as transaction passwords, private keys, mnemonics, etc., are stored locally on the user\'s mobile phone, not stored in the centralized server, so if the user forgets the password is There is no way to reset it by a third party agency such as the DiorPay team.\nThe only solution is to reset the new password by re-importing the mnemonic or private key.\nPS: Make sure the backup mnemonic or private key is correct. If you have any questions, please contact customer service.</string>
    <string name="help7">How to delete the wallet?</string>
    <string name="help7_a">Click on the phone to delete it.</string>
    <string name="help8">Can the backup wallet mnemonic be retrieved after it is lost?</string>
    <string name="help8_a">xxxxxxx</string>
    <string name="toast_code">Verification sent, please check!</string>
    <string name="toast_name">Please enter wallet name!</string>
    <string name="toast_right_code">Please enter four verification codes!</string>
    <string name="toast_register_success">Wallet successfully created!</string>
    <string name="toast_login_success">Successfully logged in!</string>
    <string name="add_asset">Add asset</string>
    <string name="miner_fee">Miner fee</string>
    <string name="toast_select_coin">This currency type has existed!</string>
    <string name="toast_copy_success">Successfully copied!</string>
    <string name="toast_add_asset_success">Successfully added asset!</string>
    <string name="toast_input_address">Please enter receiving address!</string>
    <string name="toast_input_count">Please enter amount!</string>
    <string name="toast_input_count0">Amount cannot be 0!</string>
    <string name="toast_input_count1">Entered amount is more than available amount!</string>
    <string name="toast_transform_success">Successfully transferred coins!</string>
    <string name="out">Send</string>
    <string name="in">Receive</string>
    <string name="remain">Balance</string>
    <string name="all_read">All read</string>
    <string name="transfer_notice">Transfer notice</string>
    <string name="system_message">System message</string>
    <string name="code_not_right">QR code is not the wallet address</string>
    <string name="volume">Vol: </string>
    <string name="toast_update_name">Please enter nickname!</string>
    <string name="toast_update_name1">Successfully edit nickname!</string>
    <string name="select_email">Please select mail class applications</string>
    <string name="policies_content">1. In order to provide the services of this website, the user agrees to the user registration information (including personal identification information of the user), the user\'s browser server data (including IP address, etc.) received by the website when the user visits the website page or uses the website service. ), user operation data and other user information obtained by the website through legal channels are recorded, saved and used. Except as otherwise provided in this Agreement, this Website does not provide, sell, rent, share and trade the User\'s personal information to any unrelated third parties; for the convenience of users to use the Service, the User agrees to the User\'s and/or User\'s organization of this Website. The identity and operational information are comprehensively counted; for the purpose of realizing the use of third party services displayed by the website, the user agrees and authorizes the website to provide the user\'s registration information and other user information or data under this section to third parties. This website does not disclose any information that may be used to identify the user\'s personal identity. However, this website does not assume any responsibility for the analysis of the user\'s personally identifiable information from the user\'s username or other discloseable information.\n2. The User agrees that the Site may disclose or use the User\'s personal information for the purpose of identifying and confirming the User\'s identity, or for resolving disputes, or for securing the Site, preventing or restricting illegal or criminal activity. The User agrees that this Website may disclose or use the User\'s personal information to protect the User\'s life, the security of the property or to prevent serious violations of the legitimate rights of others or the public interest. The user agrees that this website may disclose or use the user\'s personal information to improve the service of the website, and make the service of the website more in line with the requirements of the user, so that the user can get a better experience when using the website service. The user agrees that the website uses the user\'s personal information to contact the user and provides the user with information that may be of interest to the user, such as introducing, promoting products, services, promotional offers, or commercial short messages of business operations opportunities.\n3. This website will disclose the user\'s information in good faith when the website is legally mandated or provided by the government or the authority to provide the user\'s information. This website will disclose the user\'s information in good faith when the website needs to protect the rights and property of this website, the agents, customers, users and others of this website, including the implementation of the agreement, policies and terms of use of this website.\n4. The User agrees that if the Website intends to conduct, acquire, reorganize or sell all or part of the shares and/or assets, the Website reserves the right to disclose the User\'s information to the relevant parties of the aforementioned transaction with the exception of the confidentiality agreement. This website completes these transactions.\n5. This website is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content of websites other than this website.\n6. Other privacy policies are subject to the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="agreement_content">Welcome to use DiorPay wallet (WWW.DIORPAY.COM, hereinafter referred to as “this website”). This website is operated by Zhejiang Scene Blockchain Technology Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “the company”). The rights and obligations of this website under this agreement. All are enjoyed and undertaken by the company.\n\nBefore you register as a user of this website, please be sure to read all the terms of this agreement carefully. Once you click the consent registration button on the registration page of this website and complete the registration process and obtain the account number and password of this website, you are deemed to have agreed to reach the User Agreement (hereinafter referred to as “this Agreement”) with this website, and you hereby promise It is agreed to use this Agreement as the basis for determining the rights and obligations of both parties. The Company reserves the right to make any modifications and additions to the terms of this Agreement from time to time and publish it on this website. Modifications and additions to the terms of this Agreement will take effect immediately upon publication. Your continued access to and use of this website is deemed to be acceptance of this revised agreement. Otherwise, you have the right to terminate this Agreement by stopping access and refusing to use the Site, canceling your information and account number on the Site.\n\nYou are committed to abide by the laws, regulations, rules and other government regulations of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of the People\'s Republic of China and your location, do not destroy the normal operation order of Bitcoin, and do not use the services of this website to organize or participate in illegal activities such as money laundering. In the event of any legal consequences resulting from a violation, you are solely responsible for all applicable legal liabilities. The website has the right to suspend or terminate the service of the user, and has the right to be on this website and the Internet if the user has illegal or criminal acts, or if the website has relevant evidence to reasonably suspect that the user may be illegal, criminal or violates this agreement. The user is declared illegal and breach of contract, and has the right to report to the relevant authorities and cooperate with the investigation activities of the relevant authorities, including but not limited to disclosure of all user information of the user, personal data and other information under the Privacy Policy. The consequences, risks and liabilities of the website in the implementation of any and all of the above actions shall be borne by the user. By signing this Agreement, the User shall be deemed to understand and accept the above terms and shall permanently and irrevocably authorize the Website to disclose relevant information and take corresponding measures.\n\nThe Anti-Money Laundering Announcement is an integral part of this Agreement. Users accepting this Agreement shall be deemed to have accepted the entire contents of the Anti-Money Laundering Announcement. The content of this agreement includes the text of this agreement, the "Privacy Policy" and various rules, statements and instructions that have been published on this website or may be released in the future. The Privacy Policy, all rules, statements, descriptions, etc. are an integral part of this Agreement and have the same legal effect as the body of this Agreement.\n\nFirst, the definition\n1. “Bitcoin”: Bitcoin (BTC) is a legally valid virtual commodity commonly used internationally.\n2. “User”: All users of this website who have registered as users through this website.\n3. “User Registration”: The process in which the user logs into the website and fills in the relevant information as required and confirms the agreement to perform the relevant user agreement.\n\nSecond, user registration, transaction real name certification and recharge\n1. User statements and warranties:\nThe User has full civil rights and capacity and has read and agreed to this Agreement. If the user is a person with limited ability, the user states and warrants that clicking the consent to register button and registering becomes the user\'s consent or confirmation from the legal agent. When a user\'s representative office registers, logs in, and uses this website, the user states and warrants that he or she has been fully authorized to act on behalf of the organization.\n2. Registration:\n(1) The user agrees to provide valid e-mail address, contact telephone number and other information according to the requirements of the user registration page of this website, and set the account number and password of this website. The user shall ensure the authenticity, completeness and accuracy of all the information provided, and bear any information. All legal liabilities and legal consequences caused by untrue, incomplete and inaccurate.\n(2) If the user is legally, complete and effectively providing the information required for registration, he/she has the right to obtain the account number and password of this website. The account and password of this website are used for user login on this website.\n(3) When the user obtains the account number and password of the website, the user is deemed to have successfully registered, and the user agrees to receive the email and/or short message related to the management and operation of the website sent by the website.\n3. Before the user registers successfully, the Bitcoin usage related service must be provided in accordance with the certification requirements of this website, and the real ID number of the person must be photographed and uploaded, and the real name authentication is performed. After the authentication is successful, the website will assign a fixed ordinary account to the user and bind it to the user\'s username.\n\nThird, user service\nAvailable service\n(1) The User acknowledges and agrees that the Website has the right to make adjustments to the service items, service contents, etc. from time to time (including termination of some services); despite the above-mentioned service introduction and description, the services that the user can actually use are displayed and actualized by the user when using the website. The current status of available services will prevail.\n(2) The User acknowledges and confirms that the services displayed on this website may be provided by this website or provided by a third party; the services provided by third parties shall be prompted or explained by the user when using the website; the user agrees to use the third party service to comply with the third party. User Agreement, Service Rules and related regulations; the User agrees and authorizes the Website to provide the User\'s registration information on the Website and the Personal Data under the Privacy Policy to the third party for the purpose of the User\'s use of the Third Party Service; the User acknowledges and confirms Although the third party service is displayed on this website and jumps through this website, the rights, obligations, and responsibilities related to the use of the third party service by the user are exercised and assumed by the user and the third party independently of the website.\n(3) The user has the right to participate in the website activities organized by this website in accordance with the activity rules published on this website.\n2. Rules of use\n(1) The user shall abide by the provisions of all applicable laws, regulations, rules and regulatory documents, guarantee the legality of all the sources of the Bitcoin in the account, and may not engage in illegal or damage to the website or third party rights on this website or by using the services of this website. Activities, including but not limited to sending or receiving any information that violates the law, violations, violations of public order, infringement of the rights of others, sending or receiving pyramid schemes or other harmful information or statements, without the authorization of this website or forgery of this website email Header information, etc., use any activity that does not have a legal source or bitcoin to engage in any activity, or engage in any illegal activities.\n(2) Users should properly use and keep their account number and password on this website and the mobile phone number, e-mail address and verification code or verification link received by mobile phone and e-mail, as well as other information required to use the website service. . Users may not grant, borrow, rent, transfer or otherwise license or allow third parties to hold and/or use the website without the consent of this website. The user assumes full responsibility for any operation or consequence of using his or her website account and password, mobile phone verification code and other information. When the user finds that the account number, password, verification code or other information of the website is used by a third party without authorization, or if there are other account security issues, the website should be effectively notified immediately, and the website may be requested to suspend the account of the website. Service. This website reserves the right to verify, judge and take appropriate action against the user\'s request within a reasonable time. However, regardless of whether the website has independently judged whether to agree to take appropriate action, this website does not assume any risk or loss that has occurred before the action was taken. No responsibility, no commitment or liability for the decision of appropriate action and the time for appropriate action.\n3. Service suspension or termination:\nIn the event of any of the following circumstances, the Website reserves the right to suspend or terminate the provision of services to the User and to notify the User reasonably:\n(1) Perform necessary maintenance and construction on network equipment;\n(2) Sudden network equipment failure;\n(3) The network communication equipment used on this website is stopped for unexplained reasons and cannot provide services;\n(4) Due to force majeure factors, this website cannot provide online services;\n(5) Required by relevant government agencies.\N4. In the event of any of the following circumstances, the Website reserves the right to suspend or terminate the provision of services to the User at any time without prior notice to the User:(1) The personal data provided by the user is inaccurate, untrue, and illegal;\n(2) The user uses any third party program to log in or use the service;\n(3) The user abuses the rights to damage the interests of this website;\n(4) The user has harmed the behavior of other users;\n(5) The user exists or the website reasonably believes that the user violates the provisions of laws and regulations;\n(6) The user has violated social customs and social morality;\n(7) The user violates other agreements in this agreement.\n\nFourth, the rights and obligations of users\n1. The user has the right to accept the services provided by this website in accordance with this agreement.\n2. The user reserves the right to terminate the use of the website at any time, but unless otherwise agreed in the contract, the user cannot redeem the wealth management product in advance.\n3. The user has the right to transfer or transfer Bitcoin at any time (the user or the website shall, according to the agreement of this agreement, take measures such as sealing, freezing, prohibiting use, etc., as the user is suspected of committing a crime or a contractual agreement. Except for), but the corresponding handling fee must be paid to this website when transferring Bitcoin.\n4. The user is responsible for the authenticity, validity and security of the personal data provided at the time of registration.\n5. Users must not interfere with the normal conduct of Bitcoin, destroy order, and must not use any bitcoin with unclear sources or legal sources, and must not engage in any criminal activities.\n6. Users may not interfere with the normal operation of this website or interfere with the use of the services of this website by other users by any technical means or other means.\n7. If the user has a dispute with other users due to Bitcoin operation on this website, the user must apply to the judicial organ or administrative agency to retrieve relevant information from the website according to law. This website will not be responsible for providing relevant information through other channels.\n8. Users may not maliciously destroy the reputation of this website by fictitious facts, etc., and may not commit any acts that harm the legitimate rights and interests of this website.\n9. If the information network connection is faulty, the computer, communication, power or other system failure, staff error operation, etc. cause the website to repay the user and pay more bitcoin, the user is obliged to pay more The paid part is immediately returned to the original path. The user shall not complete the return within 10 days from the date of receiving reasonable notice or reminder from this website.\n\n6. Rights and obligations of this website\n1. If the user does not have the registration qualification as stipulated in this agreement, the website has the right to refuse the user to register, and the registered user has the right to cancel the user account of the website. The website has the right to the above-mentioned users for the losses suffered thereby. Or its legal representative, authorized subject or responsible entity claims compensation. At the same time, this website reserves the right to decide whether or not to accept user registration under any other circumstances.\n2. This website has the right to terminate the use of the account when it is found that the account user is not the initial registrant of the account.\n3. This website reasonably suspects that the information provided by the user is incorrect, false, invalid, incomplete or illegal, the user has harmed the behavior of other users, the user has violated social customs and social ethical behavior, or the user has other violations of this agreement. At the time of the act, the user has the right to notify the user to correct, update the information or suspend or terminate the service of the website.\n4. This website reserves the right to correct the information when it finds that there is a material error in any of the information displayed on this website.\n5. This website reserves the right to transfer, modify, suspend or terminate any service of this website at any time. The website does not need to inform the user in advance, but will notify the user of the transfer, modification, suspension or termination of any service in an appropriate manner such as announcement. And make reasonable efforts to avoid loss of user accounts.\n6. This website shall take necessary technical means and management measures to ensure the normal operation of this website, and provide necessary and reliable operating environment and services to maintain the operation order of Bitcoin.\n7. This website protects the user\'s account security by strengthening technical input, improving security and other measures. It is obliged to notify the user in advance when there is a foreseeable security risk in the user\'s account.\n8. This website reserves the right to retain the user\'s registration information and all information and data (including personal data under the Privacy Policy) during the period of performance of this agreement and after the termination of this agreement, but may not be used illegally. Such information.\n9. This website reserves the right to delete any information or content on this website that does not comply with relevant laws and regulations, regulatory documents or the provisions of this website (including any information or content posted or transmitted by any user). No need to notify the user in advance.\n10. If a user commits an illegal or criminal act, or if the website has relevant evidence to reasonably suspect that the user may be in violation of the law, crime or violation of this agreement, the website has the right to suspend or terminate the service to the user without notifying the user, the right to This website and the Internet publish the user\'s illegal and breach of contract, and have the right to record the content in any credit information and files related to the user.\n11. If a user commits an illegal or criminal act, or if the website has relevant evidence to reasonably suspect that the user may be in violation of law or crime, the website has the right to freeze all accounts of the user on the website and restrict or prohibit users from using all functions of the website. And have the right to take other necessary and reasonable measures in accordance with anti-money laundering laws and regulations and other laws and regulations. This website will actively cooperate with the police investigation to provide the authority with all registration information and operation information of the user, including but not limited to name, ID number, contact information, photos, operation records and other information.\n12. If the website suffers any reputation damage, economic loss or any expenses due to the user\'s violation of the law or the violation of the terms of this agreement, the website has the right to request the user to clarify the facts at their own expense, restore the reputation of the website, and compensate the website. The total loss or cost of the website.\n\n7. Liability exemption\nTo the extent permitted by law, this website is subject to information network equipment maintenance, information network connection failures, computer, communication or other system failures, power failures, strikes, labor disputes, riots, uprisings, riots. , terrorist attacks, earthquakes, fires, floods, storms, explosions, wars, government actions, orders of the judiciary, any force majeure or any unserviceable or delayed service caused by reasons beyond the reasonable control of this website, and users suffer as a result The loss is not responsible.\n\nEight, intellectual property rights\n1. All intellectual achievements contained in this website include, but are not limited to, website logos (logo), databases, website design, text and graphics, software, photos, software compilation, source code, applications, application programming interface copyrights, and All other copyrights and other intellectual property rights relating to this website are the property of this website. Users may not copy, alter, copy, imitate, transmit or use any of the foregoing materials or content, and may not implement, use, transfer or license others to implement the above intellectual property rights for any purpose. Any unauthorized use of the content of this website is illegal and this website will be held liable.\n2. All rights and interests (including but not limited to goodwill and trademarks, logos) included in the name of this website are owned by Zhejiang Scene Blockchain Technology Co., Ltd.\n9. Change and termination of the agreement\n1. The User agrees that the Website has the right to make changes to the contents of this Agreement or any Terms of Service, Operation Rules, etc. at any time, and to make an announcement on this website. The changes will take effect from the time of publication or the effective date of the announcement, if the user continues to use this website. The service provided is deemed to be the user\'s consent to the change. If the user does not agree to the change, he/she must immediately stop using any service on this website and cancel the account.\n2. If the user cancels the account and the website cancels the user account in accordance with the provisions of this agreement and terminates the service to the user, this agreement is terminated.\n3. Upon termination of this Agreement, the User shall not be entitled to request that the Website continue to provide any services or perform any other obligations, including but not limited to any information required to be reserved by the Website for the User or to disclose the User\'s original account to the User, or to the User or The third party forwards any information it has not read or sent.\n4. After the termination of this agreement, the user has the right to retrieve the Bitcoin in the account or to be disposed of by this website in accordance with relevant laws and regulations. All risks, losses and liabilities shall be borne by the user at the discretion of the user due to user clearance.\n\nX. Privacy Policy\n1. In order to provide the services of this website, the user agrees to the user registration information (including personal identification information of the user), the user\'s browser server data (including IP address, etc.) received by the website when the user visits the website page or uses the website service. ), user operation data and other user information obtained by the website through legal channels are recorded, saved and used. Except as otherwise provided in this Agreement, this Website does not provide, sell, rent, share and trade the User\'s personal information to any unrelated third parties; for the convenience of users to use the Service, the User agrees to the User\'s and/or User\'s organization of this Website. The identity and operational information are comprehensively counted; for the purpose of realizing the use of third party services displayed by the website, the user agrees and authorizes the website to provide the user\'s registration information and other user information or data under this section to third parties. This website does not disclose any information that may be used to identify the user\'s personal identity. However, this website does not assume any responsibility for the analysis of the user\'s personally identifiable information from the user\'s username or other discloseable information.\n2. The User agrees that the Site may disclose or use the User\'s personal information for the purpose of identifying and confirming the User\'s identity, or for resolving disputes, or for securing the Site, preventing or restricting illegal or criminal activity. The User agrees that this Website may disclose or use the User\'s personal information to protect the User\'s life, the security of the property or to prevent serious violations of the legitimate rights of others or the public interest. The user agrees that this website may disclose or use the user\'s personal information to improve the service of the website, and make the service of the website more in line with the requirements of the user, so that the user can get a better experience when using the website service. The user agrees that the website uses the user\'s personal information to contact the user and provides the user with information that may be of interest to the user, such as introducing, promoting products, services, promotional offers, or commercial short messages of business operations opportunities.\n3. This website will disclose the user\'s information in good faith when the website is legally mandated or provided by the government or the authority to provide the user\'s information. This website will disclose the user\'s information in good faith when the website needs to protect the rights and property of this website, the agents, customers, users and others of this website, including the implementation of the agreement, policies and terms of use of this website.\n4. The User agrees that if the Website intends to conduct, acquire, reorganize or sell all or part of the shares and/or assets, the Website reserves the right to disclose the User\'s information to the relevant parties of the aforementioned transaction with the exception of the confidentiality agreement. This website completes these transactions.\n5. This website is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content of websites other than this website.\n6. Other privacy policies are subject to the Privacy Policy.\n\nXI, anti-money laundering\n1. This website complies with and implements international anti-money laundering-related international treaties, laws and regulations applicable to the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (with the Drug Trafficking (Recovery of Proceeds) Ordinance and the Organized and Serious Crimes Ordinance as the core), industry supervision Regulations and guidelines (eg, anti-money laundering guidelines and operating procedures promulgated by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, guidelines for the prevention of money laundering activities), identification of users, retention of customer identity data and service records, and reports of large and suspicious operations System.\n2. When the user registers, reports the account password or the fund password, the photo of the ID card should be provided and uploaded. The website identifies and compares the identity information provided by the user. This website has reasonable grounds to suspect that users who use false identity to register or use the service have the right to refuse to register or stop the service, freeze, or cancel the registered account.\n3. This website refers to the relevant standards, rules and guidelines of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, as well as other applicable laws and regulations, saves large operations and operational records suspected of money laundering, reports suspicious operations to the regulatory authorities, and is in the regulatory body. Provided to the regulatory body when a record is requested.\n4. This website preserves user identity information and large and suspicious operational records, assists in accordance with the law, cooperates with judicial organs and administrative law enforcement agencies to combat money laundering activities, and assists judicial organs, customs, taxation and other departments to inquire and freeze in accordance with laws and regulations. And deductions and other measures.\n5. According to the relevant anti-money laundering policy and to protect the security of customer assets, the name of the sender must be the same as the real name certification.\n6. If this website discovers or receives reports from others or complains that the user exists or may have behaviors prohibited by anti-money laundering laws and regulations, this website has the right to freeze, ban, cancel, etc. the user account, and not to implement the above actions to the user. Take any responsibility.\n\nTwelve, risk tips\n1. The Internet is a global public network that is decentralized and not controlled by any one agency. The way data is transmitted over the Internet is not completely certain and may be subject to unlawful interference or intrusion. Data transmitted over the Internet may be obtained or tampered with by some unauthorised individual, group or institution through certain channels. Data transmission over the Internet may be delayed due to heavy traffic, or interruptions, stalls, incomplete data, data errors, etc. for other reasons, causing errors, delays, interruptions, or stalls in the data or its transmission. The user\'s online identity may be leaked or spoofed, and the user\'s own negligence may cause the account or password to be leaked, which may cause loss to the user. The computer used by the user may have an impact on the user\'s login, operation time or operation data due to performance defects, quality problems, computer viruses, hardware failures and other reasons, causing losses to the user. The loss or liability caused by the above risks shall be borne by the user and this website shall not be responsible for any. Nevertheless, in the attitude of being responsible to users, this website will adopt advanced network products and technical measures to maximize the protection of user data and operational activities.\n2. Bitcoin operations are extremely risky. The Bitcoin market is brand new, unconfirmed, and may not grow. At present, Bitcoin is mainly used by speculators in large quantities, and the retail and commercial markets are relatively less used, so bitcoin prices are prone to fluctuations, which in turn adversely affect bitcoin operations. The Bitcoin market has no upside limit and trading is open 24 hours. Due to the small number of chips, Bitcoin is easily controlled by the dealer and may experience a skyrocketing or plunging situation. Involving Bitcoin operations, users should control their own risk, evaluate the operating value and operational risk of Bitcoin, and bear the economic risks of losing all operations. Due to the formulation or modification of relevant laws, regulations and regulatory documents, the operation of Bitcoin is suspended or prohibited, so the economic losses caused by the users are all borne by the users.\n3. Once the user registers on this website, the user is fully aware of and understands the risks of operating and using other services on this website, and agrees to bear the risks or losses that may occur.\n\nXIII. Liability for breach of contract\n1. A user who violates the agreement of this agreement constitutes a breach of contract and the user shall be liable for breach of contract.\n2. If the information provided by the user is untrue, incomplete or inaccurate, causing loss to the website, the website has the right to request the user to compensate for the loss of the website.\n3. If the user violates the laws and regulations or the agreement of this agreement, the website has the right to immediately terminate the service of providing the website, cancel the account number, and demand compensation for this. The damage caused by this website.\n4 If the user interferes with the operation of this website by technical means or interferes with the use of this website by other users, this website has the right to immediately cancel the account of this website and has the right to demand compensation for the damage caused to this website.\n5. If the user maliciously destroys the reputation of the website or other acts that damage the reputation of the website by fictitious facts, etc., the website has the right to request the user to publicly apologize to the website, compensate him for the losses caused to the website, and have the right. Termination of the provision of this website service.\n6. The User agrees that in any case, the scope of liability of the Website to the User is limited to the direct loss of the User (including reasonable legal fees and other expenses incurred by the User for claiming breach of contract), excluding any estimated income or profit. Loss, loss due to loss of contract opportunity, loss due to data disclosure or theft, or any special or indirect loss; and in addition to any intentional or gross negligence on this website, in any case, this website The total amount of any liability for breach of contract to the user shall not exceed the total amount of the service fee paid by the user to or from the paying party of the relevant service. Both parties confirmed that the limit was set in the case of compensation for loss, because the website cannot foresee the loss of the user when entering into this agreement; if the user\'s loss may be greater than the compensation limit stipulated in this article, the user shall inform this website when signing this agreement. The website will determine the service price according to the risk and negotiate with the user.\n\nXIV. Dispute resolution\n1. Disputes arising from the provision of services on this website are governed by the laws of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region.\n2. Any dispute, dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement shall be decided by the Hong Kong International Arbitration Centre (HKIAC) in accordance with the arbitration rules in effect at that time.\n3. Any legal relationship or legal dispute between the user and other users of this website or other website users due to the operation of Bitcoin or the use of the services of this website shall not be legally liable for this website, and shall be resolved by both parties.\n\nXV. Effectiveness and interpretation of the agreement\n1. This Agreement is effective when the user clicks on the registration of the registration page of this website and completes the registration process and obtains the account number and password of this website. It is binding on both this website and the user.\n2. If some of the terms of this Agreement are deemed invalid or unenforceable, the other terms of this Agreement will remain in effect.\n3. If any additional terms of service, rules of use or instructions published by the Website in connection with the specific service are inconsistent with the body of this Agreement, the additional terms of service, rules of use or instructions shall prevail under the specific service.\n4. The final interpretation of this Agreement is the property of this website.\n\nXVI. Complaints and consultations\nThis website establishes a professional customer service team to provide users with timely troubleshooting and complaint feedback. If you have any questions, complaints or inquiries during the use of this website, you can always send an email to the designated email address of this website: BD@DIORPAY.COM</string>
    <string name="update_pwd">Password successfully Changed!</string>
    <string name="add_wallet">Please add wallet!</string>
    <string name="trust">Never let down your trust.</string>
    <string name="trade_record">Transaction details</string>
    <string name="in_address">Receivable address</string>
    <string name="out_address">Transfer address</string>
    <string name="poundage">Poundage</string>
    <string name="block_height">Block height</string>
    <string name="trade_number">Trade number</string>
    <string name="trade_type">Trade type</string>
    <string name="coin_out">Transfer</string>
    <string name="coin_in">Receive</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="record">Update log</string>
    <string name="log_info">Log info</string>
    <string name="sure_ing">Confirmation</string>
    <string name="finish">Success</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="read_finish">All set to read!</string>
    <string name="toast_upload_avatar">Avatar successfully upload!</string>
    <string name="is_register">The phone number has been registered!</string>
</resources>
